Carole Kern

Beauty specialist with over ten years experience in a retail setting / Esthetician.

Horsham, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Carole-Kern/ab9301697a772dab

My goal is to become associated with a company where I can utilize my skills and gain further experience while enhancing the company's productivity and reputation.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Fashion Consultant

Ann Inc - Philadelphia, PA - November 2012 to Present

Acknowledged and greeted guest with prompt and friendly service

Placed special merchandise orders for customers

Received and processed cash and credit payments for in store purchases

Prestige Consultant

Ulta Salon, Cosmetics & Fragrance Inc - Plymouth Meeting, PA - November 2010 to August 2011

Makeup application, skincare analysis, product demonstration

Booked appointments for scheduled special events

Stocked shelves, rotated products, followed plan-o-grams

Counter Manager

Boscov's - Plymouth Meeting, PA - July 2006 to February 2009

Trained and educated sales staff on industry

Coordinated all purchasing and maintained inventory controls

Regularly exceeded projected sales goals

Beauty Specialist

Strawbridge's - Philadelphia, PA - March 2001 to August 2005

Established and supported excellent customer service

Maintained client files through careful documentation

Achieved personal selling and service goals

EDUCATION

Business

Horsham High School - Horsham, PA 1980

SKILLS

Licensed Esthetician # CQ115383 / Skin care analysis / Makeup application/ Excellent customer service philosophy/Team player/ Fast learner/ Reliable and dependable.